<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:rawvoice="http://www.rawvoice.com/rawvoiceRssModule/" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Lost Chronicles: Secrets of Greycastle</title>
        <link>https://bit.ly/secretsofgreycastle</link>
        <image>
            <url>https://www.notion.so/image/https%3A%2F%2Fprod-files-secure.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F8f01c03f-0588-4d9f-a3dd-38b06c8eb0f8%2F17d3ae49-4b18-4add-9e46-7bfb7c90bea6%2FThe_Lost_Chronicles_-_Secrets_of_Greycastle_-_Album_Arts.png?table=block&id=1711018f-a856-8076-994d-e536df2ff055&spaceId=8f01c03f-0588-4d9f-a3dd-38b06c8eb0f8&width=2000&userId=fc659b30-0328-406b-ac67-e2ab40bcef29&cache=v2</url>
            <title>The Lost Chronicles: Secrets of Greycastle</title>
            <link>https://bit.ly/secretsofgreycastle</link>
        </image>
        <description>
            Welcome to The Lost Chronicles: Secrets of Greycastle, a thrilling TTRPG podcast where intrigue, danger, and adventure collide! Join our daring heroes as they embark on a journey in the Draw Steel! RPG system, developed by MCDM. Our story begins when a shadowy figure named Jethro hires the party for a seemingly simple task: deliver a mysterious cargo to the town of Greycastle—without ever peeking inside. But when disaster strikes and the cart is destroyed, the secret contents unravel a web of mystery far more sinister than they could have imagined. With each dice roll, the stakes rise higher, and the secrets of Greycastle grow darker. Tune in for epic storytelling, dynamic characters, and edge-of-your-seat action in this immersive tabletop adventure!
        </description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Braeden Perkins copyright 2025</copyright>
        <item>
		    <title>Unexpected Cargo - Quest 1 | Secrets of Greycastle</title>
		    <link>
		        https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/8il1zq2grbxiqs57ocuda/Quest-1-Unexpected-Cargo.mp3
		    </link>
		    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:00:00 MDT</pubDate>
		    <description>
		        In the gritty, crime-ridden town of Burlington, five unlikely heroes cross paths in a dimly lit tavern. Amid whispered conversations and clinking glasses, they are approached by a mysterious man named Jethro, who offers them a lucrative but enigmatic job: deliver a locked cargo to the distant town of Greycastle. The rules are simple—don’t ask questions, and under no circumstances, open the cargo. However, as the group sets out, they quickly realize they aren’t alone. A relentless, mysterious adversary is hot on their trail, determined to claim the cargo for themselves. With danger looming and trust still fragile, the party must navigate this perilous beginning to uncover the secrets that await. Will they succeed, or has Jethro’s offer pulled them into something far more dangerous than they could have foreseen?
		    </description>
		    <enclosure url="https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/8il1zq2grbxiqs57ocuda/Quest-1-Unexpected-Cargo.mp3" length="36715125" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		    <guid>
		        https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/8il1zq2grbxiqs57ocuda/Quest-1-Unexpected-Cargo.mp3
		    </guid>
		</item>
		<item>
		    <title>Demons and Gods - Quest 2 | Secrets of Greycastle</title>
		    <link>
		        https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/2r35tpvtxvlvdst7ztxez/Quest-2-Demons-and-Gods.mp3
		    </link>
		    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		    <description>
		        Fresh off their victory over a band of ratfolk bandits, our heroes continue their journey to Greycastle. Their path leads them to the quiet homestead of Jebediah and his family, where they find a brief moment of rest and conversation. But peace is short-lived. The shadows grow long as their relentless pursuers catch up—revealing themselves to be far more sinister than expected. Demons emerge from the darkness, threatening not only the party but the innocent family caught in the crossfire. Will our heroes rise to protect Jebediah's homestead, or will the darkness claim another victim?
		    </description>
		    <enclosure url="https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/2r35tpvtxvlvdst7ztxez/Quest-2-Demons-and-Gods.mp3" length="36715125" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		    <guid>
		        https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/2r35tpvtxvlvdst7ztxez/Quest-2-Demons-and-Gods.mp3
		    </guid>
		</item>
    </channel>
</rss>
